
<?xml-model href="CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Oh! You aren't exactly how I imagined... but that's okay! I'm Jodi. It's a quiet little town, so it's very exciting when someone new moves in! Having a farmer around could really change things."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Entering:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"What a treat!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Leaving:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"I think I'll make seafood tonight."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"The view is breathtaking! Deep blue as far as the eye can see..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Bar:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"We all love it when Gus shows up."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>reject_864:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"What's this? It looks like one of Kent's buddies from the war. Maybe you should show it to him?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Maintaining a household is difficult work... but somebody has to do it. Yes?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon6:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"It's nice to have a family... but I'd be lying if I said I never miss the freedom of being young..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>2_1:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"My husband Kent is a soldier, working overseas. That's why he's not here right now. I know he'll come back safe once his tour is over!! Need something?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Exercise is important for staying healthy. I always make sure to set aside some time for it. As a parent, I don't have much time to devote to myself. So I try and make every minute count."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed4:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"I wish I could spend more time outside, but there's so much work to do. I started wearing rubber gloves to keep my hands soft. The older you get, the more work you have to do to stay healthy. Ok, bye!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"What did you say? It's  already? My goodness! I still have tons of work to do!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu6:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Where does all the time go? *sigh* I remember when Sam was a little baby wearing diapers. He was such a cute little kid. Don't tell him I said that. You must really like talking to me, huh?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"So you're a farmer, huh? Interesting.I've never met a farmer before. Maybe some day you can teach me how to grow vegetables."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"The food at JojaMart might not be the healthiest for my family, but with such low prices you'd be crazy to shop anywhere else! The food at Pierre's is so much fresher and healthier than anything I ever bought at JojaMart. I do miss those cheap Joja prices, though."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Hi. Need something?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat4:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"I'm so glad you're trying to improve that old farm. Once you've got everything in order, it's going to add a lot to our community! It's going to be a lot of work for you, though. Bye."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon2:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Yesterday I visited Yoba's Altar to give thanks for my husband's safe return. Yesterday I visited Yoba's Altar to ask for my husband's safe return. I'm trying to stay positive, but it's hard sometimes."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"I'm taking a break from house chores today. I'm taking the day off. If I don't spend any time outside, I'll go crazy! Plus I don't want my legs to turn soft."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun8:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"I had a dream that I had complete freedom, no obligation to anyone but myself... ...Then I woke up and realized I had a full day of house chores ahead of me... But I don't regret having a family, @... Sam and Vincent mean everything to me!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Summer is nice, but it also means more work. I'll have to keep the garden in shape on top of working in the house!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Hello. Do you need something? I'm a little busy."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Tue_inlaw_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"How's my little Sammy doing on the old farm?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Housework is frustrating because you're never finished. The day after I sweep the floor, it's dirty again."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"What in the world am I going to make for dinner? *sigh*..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Maybe I've spoiled the boys a bit. They've never had to do any chores. I guess I want them to be able to enjoy their childhood while they still can. Well, Sam's basically a man now, though. I hope he hasn't grow up to be lazy. That won't do. Being a parent isn't very easy."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Thu_inlaw_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Is Sam just bumming around the farm, or is he contributing?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Caroline and I are good friends. I tell her everything."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sun2:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"When you become a parent, you have to leave your old lifestyle behind. Maybe that's not entirely true... but if you're not careful, it will happen."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"I loved playing in the snow when I was a kid. The great thing about being a mother is that I get to enjoy it again."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Hi. Do you get tired of people asking about your farm all the time? I think I would."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Tue6:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"*sigh*... Sometimes I dream about life on my own... without a family to look after. Is that horrible? Don't tell anyone."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Wed2:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"What do I do for fun? Hmm... That's a good question. I like sleeping."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Wed4_2:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Kent has been home for a while now, but he still seems uneasy."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"Sam makes a lot of noise with that music of his. I hope it doesn't disturb the neighbors."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Thu_inlaw_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"How's Sam doing? I have to admit, there's less cooking and cleaning to do since he moved out..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Thu8:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"We kind of rushed into our marriage, with Kent being a soldier and all... I hardly got a taste of youth and freedom, and now it's too late to ever go back. I can't believe I'm saying this to you."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"It would be nice to take a vacation once in a while..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">"If I was rich the first thing I'd do would be to hire a maid and a chef. My goodness, that would be nice!"</dialogue> </p>

</xml>