
<?xml-model href="CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>4:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"I saw a big mango floating in the sky. Linus told me it was a hot-air balloon! I thought only birds could fly..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>18:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"When I first arrived, Linus made me a suit out of leaves, like his... But I looked funny... like a fuzzy mango! I think I'll stick to my feathers."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>LeoDeparture:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"I need to find some place to live... But I have a plan... I'm going to rely on my friends."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu8:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"It felt bad at first... to leave the island and set foot in a strange land. But, I got used to it after a while. I'm a very flexible person!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu10:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"I felt like a stranger here, at first. But I've made a lot of friends! For once, I feel like I belong..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"Miss Penny is doing her best to get me up to speed in my schooling. She's really nice... ...Luckily, I remember some things from my old, old life... before washing up on the island... so it's not as difficult as it could be. Miss Penny says she's impressed with how much I know!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue10:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"I'm sure Jas and Vincent thought I was weird, at first. I accidentally squawked at the school table a few times... that didn't help. It was a big change for everyone. But we're good friends now!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"Between Linus and Miss Penny, I'm going to learn everything there is to learn! Mayor Lewis says I'm on the fast track to becoming a 'well-rounded citizen'... whatever that means."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"Have you ever noticed all the interesting birds that live here? If you listen closely, they might tell you something."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"The birds of this valley don't mind the cold so much. I'm a little jealous of their warm coats..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"Linus has been teaching me about all the wild food in the valley. There's a lot of good stuff out here! Though... I do kind of miss having golden walnuts for breakfast every morning..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"Linus taught me how to make a special spice berry rubbed fish... He says if I eat enough of it it'll keep me warm this winter!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri8:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"Uncle Linus says I should 'cook' my fish before eating it... I'm having a hard time getting used to it... so dry..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"Hey, @. Nice to see you back on the island, just like old times. This is fun! You know, I was scared when you first arrived... I knew my life was about to change."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"You know, Stardew Valley might be my new home... but the island will always be my home, too. It's nice to be able to come back and visit."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"Maybe some day, I'll visit Zuzu City... But I'm not even close to being ready, yet. This world is already so strange to me, and I'm very comfortable here right now!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun10:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"The parrots want me to thank you for all the golden walnuts you've found. They're really enjoying them."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat10:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">"@? Um... I'm a little embarrassed to ask... But... do you think Jas would ever like a guy like me? Or am I too weird? Hahaha... who cares. I'll figure it out some day."</dialogue> </p>

</xml>