
<?xml-model href="CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"Hey, you're pretty good at mining, for a human."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"I got all this stuff from the surface. I just take it from your people during the night. Hmm? What is this concept you call \"private property\"?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"Ah... cave carrot stew, cave carrot roast, cave carrot soup and cave carrots au gratin. ...And a ramekin of cave carrot brulee to sweeten the night. What?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"Hey, wanna buy something?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed_6:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"Long ago, my people knew the secrets of advanced technology. The archaeological evidence proves that. But I wonder where it came from? And where did it all go? I guess some questions will never be answered..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu_4:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"I feel most comfortable underground. The deeper underground the better."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"You've never seen a dwarf before, have you?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat_8:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"The mines can be a treacherous place. Be careful, friend."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"It's dangerous in the mines. Why don't you buy a few things from my shop to ensure your safety?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"One day you'll have to tell me about this beverage you call \"milk\"."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"You're not a spy sent by the Shadow People, are you? I'm keeping my eye on you."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri_2:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">"Most humans fear the unknown... that's why I've hidden my shop here. Your mining skills prove you're trustworthy."</dialogue> </p>

</xml>