
<?xml-model href="CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue>"Ooh!... I can read it on your face. You're going to love it here in Pelican Town.#$b#If you're ever looking for something to do in the evening, stop by the saloon. That's where I work!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Entering:</context> <dialogue>"Oh, I like this place! It's full of parrots!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Leaving:</context> <dialogue>"Ah... my lungs feel perfect."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Shore:</context> <dialogue>"Can you feel it? The ocean has a profound healing energy."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Chair:</context> <dialogue>"Are you having fun, @? You need to remember to take breaks now and then too!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Bar:</context> <dialogue>"It's nice to be on this side of the bar for once!$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort:</context> <dialogue>"If you open your heart to the sun, you can feel a loving energy inside of you.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Dance:</context> <dialogue>"%Emily is lost in the music."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>danceRejection:</context> <dialogue>"I'm very sorry... but I've already agreed to dance with someone else.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>divorced:</context> <dialogue>"@... You broke my heart... I just can't talk to you anymore.$s#$e#Please, let me try to heal...$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>dumped_Girls:</context> <dialogue>"...$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>breakUp:</context> <dialogue>"B...But I thought we had a special bond... *sniff*$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>reject_866:</context> <dialogue>"Oh, that's beautiful... I have a friend who would love that! But she lives far from here..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>secondChance_Girls:</context> <dialogue>"@... I'm ready to give you a second chance. I still have faith that there's a good person inside of you.$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue>"Have I told you Haley and I are sisters? Strange, isn't it?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon2:</context> <dialogue>"I have a secret hobby, but I won't say any more.#$e#Maybe I'll show you some day.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon4:</context> <dialogue>"This world is full of spirits and magic... Some don't believe me, but I know it's true.#$e#I can see it in your eyes... you believe in the other world, like me."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon6:</context> <dialogue>"I wish Haley would get a job or at least contribute to cooking and cleaning.$s#$e#I think she's hoping to marry someone rich.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon6_inlaw_Haley:</context> <dialogue>"I have to say, now that Haley's gone I've had a much easier time keeping things in order."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon8:</context> <dialogue>"There's good people in this town who just can't seem to find happiness. It makes me sad.$u#$e#Working in the saloon, I hear first-hand about everyone's problems.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue>"I work part-time at Gus' saloon. It pays the bills."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue4:</context> <dialogue>"I'm just working at Gus' to make ends meet... but my real passion is tailoring.$u#$e#I made these clothes from scratch, see?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue6:</context> <dialogue>"Oh, hi... It's nice of you to visit me like this.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue8:</context> <dialogue>"You know, @... I think the future looks bright for both of us."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue>"I've heard rumors of rare and powerful magic rings, forged long ago by forgotten civilizations. I'm not sure if it's true or just a fairy tale."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed4:</context> <dialogue>"You catch fish? I just hope you treat the poor things humanely.$s#$e#Every critter deserves our respect, even the slimy ones."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed6:</context> <dialogue>"Have faith... every day you're taking one more step on the path of your destiny."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed8:</context> <dialogue>"Hi, @.$u#$e#I always knew we'd become close like this..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue>"I hope you're farming in a sustainable way. The valley's ecosystem is fragile!#$e#How do I know? I have a strong gut-feeling!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu4:</context> <dialogue>"Sometimes the flowers speak to me... each one has a different story to tell!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue>"Ah, spring. The season of pastels. I actually prefer jewel tones, myself.#$b#Oh, excuse me! I was mumbling about fashion again, wasn't I?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue>"I like making my own clothes, but it's not easy to get cloth.#$e#And it's such a long trip to the city."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat6:</context> <dialogue>"Do you ever think about the texture of fabric, @? Each texture has a distinct personality... feel my dress... see?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue>"Hi @!#$e#Do you raise sheep in your barn? You can turn their wool into beautiful bolts of cloth!#$e#You'll need a loom, though. You can make them yourself if you know the crafting recipe."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun4:</context> <dialogue>"This house was left in our care by my parents. They've been traveling the world for the last two years.#$e#We have no idea when they'll be back.#$e#I enjoy living here, though. It's a beautiful area and the town is nice."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_dance1:</event></context> <dialogue>"Thank you!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_dance2:</event></context> <dialogue>"Um... Okay. Sorry you didn't like it. I guess those three years of practice were a complete waste...$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_dance3:</event></context> <dialogue>"Did you really think so? That's exactly the effect I was shooting for!$h#$b#I'm so glad you liked it."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"Haley is a picky eater. It's so hard to cook for her."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Mon4:</date></context> <dialogue>"Eating healthy is very important to me. I want to live a long and active life."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Mon_inlaw_Haley:</context> <dialogue>"Haley and I get along much better now that she's moved out. I look forward to her visits!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Tue:</context> <dialogue>"Hello there, @.#$e#I feel lazy today.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Tue6:</date></context> <dialogue>"I feel bad for Linus. People judge him, but he's just living a different lifestyle.$u#$e#I wish everyone could learn to be accepting of others."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Sun6:</date></context> <dialogue>"Hi, @! We've become decent friends, haven't we?$h#$e#That's fine with me. You're a cool guy.^I'm glad.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Sun8:</date></context> <dialogue>"Hi, @! We've become decent friends, haven't we?$h#$e#This may sound weird, but I've always been certain this would happen."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Wed:</context> <dialogue>"It doesn't rain much in summer, does it?#$e#That just means more watering work for you, huh?#$e#Or do you enjoy the sunny weather?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Thu:</context> <dialogue>"I consider the bees and butterflies to be my special friends!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"If I wasn't so busy I'd come help you on the farm!#$e#But Gus would be upset if I had another job...$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Fri6:</date></context> <dialogue>"You know, I'm sure Gus would understand if I wanted to leave the Saloon someday.#$b#There's so much out there, I can't stay a barmaid forever.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"Don't overwork yourself or you might end up in Harvey's clinic!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"Hi @!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Sun4:</date></context> <dialogue>"It's around this time of year that my good friends visit the region... I mean the parrots!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_1:</date></context> <dialogue>"Well, fall is here. Time to plant some new crops, huh?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"It's good weather for a picnic, isn't it?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Mon8:</date></context> <dialogue>"If I didn't have to work I'd suggest we go on a nice picnic!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Tue:</context> <dialogue>"Hello. Did you have a good summer?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Tue4:</date></context> <dialogue>"Hi @! I bet your farm did great this past summer, huh?#$e#You're an excellent farmer.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Wed:</context> <dialogue>"My friend runs a shop in the desert. If you ever go there stop in and say hi for me.#$e#I think she sells some rare products."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Thu:</context> <dialogue>"Are you friends with Clint? He's a nice guy, if you get to know him.#$e#He gets lonely working in his shop all day. But he's so shy he has trouble making new friends."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Thu8:</date></context> <dialogue>"I think Clint's mad at me. He never looks at me anymore...$u#$e#I always thought we were friends.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"Another beautiful fall day.#$e#It's a pity it'll soon be over."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Fri6:</date></context> <dialogue>"Smell that clean air? It's lovely, isn't it?#$b#I just fear that the Joja Co.'s of the world will take this away from us.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"Keep your mind open and some interesting things might take root.#$e#Anyway, how is your day going?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Sat6:</date></context> <dialogue>"I don't have any huge plans for life. I prefer not to stress about the future."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"Nothing like a sunny sunday to lift the spirits!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Sun6:</date></context> <dialogue>"There's so many invisible barriers holding us back. Why can't people learn to let go and celebrate freedom?#$e#Me? Well, you know what they say... 'You can't cage a wild Junimo'."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Sun10:</date></context> <dialogue>"You're such a nice person, @! Thanks for being my friend.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"Be careful an icicle doesn't fall on your head!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_Mon10:</date></context> <dialogue>"Be careful an icicle doesn't fall on your head! I wouldn't want you to get hurt!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Tue:</context> <dialogue>"Oh, hello @!$h#$e#You must be getting very good at farming by now, huh?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_Tue2:</date></context> <dialogue>"I bet you're an excellent farmer by now!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_Tue4:</date></context> <dialogue>"I think my hair is frozen solid...$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Wed:</context> <dialogue>"Haley and I aren't made for such a big house. It's a hassle to keep it clean.#$e#Ah well. I really shouldn't be complaining.#$e#Your farmhouse seems nice and cozy.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Thu:</context> <dialogue>"It must be so cold for the poor fish.$s#$e#I wonder if any fish hibernate? Maybe I should ask Demetrius."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"If I wasn't so busy I'd help you dig around in that cave by the lake.#$e#I bet there are some powerful crystals inside there."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"Do you know how to cook 'Bean Hotpot'?#$e#I like that dish quite a bit.$h%revealtasteEmily207#$e#It's hard to get fresh ingredients in the winter, huh?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"Hi!#$e#...Yes?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_Sun6:</date></context> <dialogue>"My sister and I might fight sometimes, but I would really miss her if she left.#$e#I think she'll become a very nice young lady some day... Don't tell her I said that.$h#$e#So, is there anything you want to talk about?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sun6_inlaw_Haley:</context> <dialogue>"Say hi to my sister for me! And remind her to visit me tomorrow."</dialogue> </p>
</xml>
