
<?xml-model href="MainRNC.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue>"Well hello there! I'm Gus, chef and owner of the Stardrop Saloon.#$e#Stop in if you need any refreshments. I've always got hot coffee and cold beer at the ready.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>accept_865:</context> <dialogue>"*sniff* sniff* ... that sharp smell!#$b#*slurp* *slurp* ... that zesty taste! That gritty texture!#$b#It can only be gourmet tomato salt! I'll trade you for it."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Resort_Entering:</context> <dialogue>"Hey, @! Glad you're here. I'm gonna be serving up some good stuff from behind the bar."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Resort_Leaving:</context> <dialogue>"I'll see you back home, @."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Resort:</context> <dialogue>"Meet me at the bar if you need a beverage."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>IslandSouth_14_21:</context> <dialogue>"Hey, need a drink? I've got some special beverages that showcase local ingredients from this island.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>willyCrabs:</context> <dialogue>"These might be the best crab cakes I've ever made..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue>"Yeah, I know a lot about the people living here.#$e#That's one of the benefits of being a bartender.$h#$e#Sometimes I hear too much..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>pamHouseUpgrade:</context> <dialogue>"Hey. I heard what you did for Pam. That was really really nice of you!$h#$e#Sadly, I don't think it will get her to cut back on the 'beverages'..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>pamHouseUpgradeAnonymous:</context> <dialogue>"I saw Pam earlier today... she was grinning from ear to ear! She said someone bought her a new house!#$e#Whoever it was, they truly deserve the best!$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Saloon:</context> <dialogue>"Good evening. Can I get you anything?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Saloon4:</context> <dialogue>"Good evening. Make yourself at home."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>SeedShop_Entry:</context> <dialogue>"Hi, Pierre!/Now, what do I need.../Ah, that looks good!/Makin' my special sauce tonight!/Pierre! What's fresh?/Pierre! Waddya got for me?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Saloon8:</context> <dialogue>"Hi there @. I'm glad to see you! You're always welcome here."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Saloon_Tue:</context> <dialogue>"Hi! Please relax and enjoy yourself."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Saloon_Thu:</context> <dialogue>"Hey, you look like you could use a beverage."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Saloon_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"Business has been really good tonight. I'm pleased."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue>"I sell different dishes each week, so make sure and check in every now and then!#$e#You might taste something spectacular.$h#$e#Just let me know if you have any allergies.$s#$e#Okay, see you around."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue>"Emily's been working here for a while now. I don't know what I'd do without her!#$e#I would hate to have to clean all those pots by myself.$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue>"Pam and Clint come into the saloon almost every night.#$e#I'd probably go out of business if they stopped coming.$h#$e#So make sure you don't drive them away!"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Thu6:</context> <dialogue>"Clint comes into the saloon almost every night and sits at the same table by himself.#$e#Sometimes he glances over at Emily with a nervous look. Hmmm.#$e#Maybe that's why he comes in so often. Oh well, that means more business for me."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Thu8:</context> <dialogue>"Pam comes into the saloon almost every night and drinks way too much beer.#$e#Ah well, I shouldn't pass judgement on my customers."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue>"Hi there, @. If you're ever thirsty, the Saloon is the place to be."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Fri4:</context> <dialogue>"I don't actually drink very much myself. I'm mainly doing this to make a living.#$e#Although I do enjoy a taste of the Stardew Valley vintage from time to time."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue>"Are you much of a chef, @?#$e#If you have a kitchen and some recipes, you can cook some useful dishes.#$e#Home-cooked meals make great gifts, as well."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue>"Business has been pretty steady thanks to my regular customers."</dialogue> #!String</p>

</xml>