
<?xml-model href="../RelaxNG/CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Oh... you're that new farmer boy, aren't you? Oh... You're that new farmer girl, or whatever. Aren't you? Huh? Oh... I'm Haley. Hmm... If it weren't for those horrendous clothes you might actually be cute. Hmm... If it weren't for those horrendous clothes you might actually be pretty... Actually, nevermind."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Entering:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I saw a dolphin on the way in!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Leaving:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"There's something about the sun that just makes me feel good."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Shore:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"It's strange the places life can take you... who knows what other lands are out there?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Shore_2:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Wow, look at how the sunlight sparkles on the horizon! I bet the sunsets here would make for an amazing photo. I have to remember to bring my camera next time."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Towel:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Getting the perfect tan is an artform... It's kind of like toasting a marshmallow... you have to rotate the body just right."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Towel_2:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Laying out on a tropical beach. *sigh* I think I've finally found my place in the universe. But I guess Stardew Valley's not such a bad place either!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Towel_3:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Emily's friend had this swimsuit shipped to me from all the way out in Zuzu City. City fashion is on a whole different level, isn't it?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Chair:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I painted my toenails blue to match the sea. What do you think? *wiggle* *wiggle*"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Bar:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Gus made a cute, fruity drink just for me!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"This is such a perfect beach. I'd stay here forever if I could!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>danceRejection:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Ew... No."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>divorced:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I'll be fine on my own... Thanks for the memories. Why are you still clinging to me? Go live your own life."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>breakUp:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Agh! Oh... hmph. Beat me to it, huh? Alright..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>dumped_Girls:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I've got nothing to say to you!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>secondChance_Girls:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Alright, alright... I'm done giving you the cold shoulder. Just promise me you'll never, ever lie to me again."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"This town is so small. It sucks. I have to drive, like, twenty miles to buy any decent clothes. That's why I usually just order online. What?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Nice shoes. Nice makeup. Are those made out of plastic? Or wait... Are you even wearing any? I'm bored."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"The only thing I like about this town is the beach."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I've decided I am going to organize my clothes today. I'll have to throw out all of last year's styles to make room for the new ones! *sigh* I could really go for a cupcake right now. Do you need something?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri2:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Don't you get tired of running around on that farm all day, or whatever it is you do? I couldn't stand getting all dirty like that. You probably get a nice tan, though."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I'm feeling an urge to go shopping. Ugh! I wish there was a mall here."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"My sister is so weird. Sometimes I wonder if we're actually related."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed8:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"There are only two things I like about this town. One of them is the beach. The other one is a secret! *giggle*"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue2:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I wonder if any nice shells washed up on the beach this morning? This isn't the best time of year for shells, though."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed4:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I'm glad that the flowers are starting to bloom. Those pink ones smell so good."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri6:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I need to find some kind of hobby other than shopping. I've decided I want to expand my horizons. Maybe I should learn to play the mini-harp?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon6:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I used to complain about this town being so small, but I've grown to like it. If it was much bigger it wouldn't feel like a community."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu6:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I cooked dinner last night. It actually turned out okay! But I did make a huge mess in the kitchen..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun6:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I'm thinking about donating a bunch of clothes... I must have a hundred pairs of shoes."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat8:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Yesterday I found a seagull with her wing caught in a net. I set her free, of course. She looked so helpless, the poor thing. You know, I should probably start exercising more... this youthful metabolism won't last forever."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri10:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"@, can we go on a camping trip someday? The most exotic place I've been is Zuzu city."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_clean1:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"*sigh*..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_clean2:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"NO!! I'm not going to do it! You guys are both stupid!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_clean3:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"She should take the 'high road'? What's that supposed to mean? You think I'm being a baby, huh?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_jar1:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Great, then you shouldn't have any problem opening this jar for me!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_jar2:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Oh... you aren't? Hmmm... Well could you try opening this jar for me anyways?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_darkroom1:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Aw, thanks!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_darkroom2:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Oh! I thought you knew. This room's for developing photos."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_darkroom3:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Is that so...?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_darkroom4:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Aw, thanks!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_darkroom5:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Oh! I thought you knew. This room's for developing photos."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_darkroom6:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Is that so...?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_beach1:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"No, you won't! This bracelet was passed down to me by my great-grandmother!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_beach2:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"*sigh* ...Maybe it'll wash up on another shore. I can't bear to think of it at the bottom of the ocean."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_room1:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Him? No! ...Well, I guess I used to like Alex. But not anymore! He's immature."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_room2:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"What? That sounds fun, but I wouldn't want to leave Stardew Valley right now..."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>Event_room3:</event></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Huh? What's an android?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I'm going to get such a nice tan this summer."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Ew, you're all dirty."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Wed:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Um... Yes? I didn't hear you, I'm thinking about something else."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_10:</date></context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Do you have baby bunnies on your farm? Bunnies are SO cute! &lt;"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"If you stay in the sun a lot it'll make your hair lighter. It's a good thing to know!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"I wonder what Alex is doing today... Huh? I didn't notice you standing there."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sat:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">"Farming sounds so boring... What do you even do all day?</dialogue> </p>
</xml>
