
<?xml-model href="CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"A stranger?... Hello. Don't mind me. I just live out here alone."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>reject_869:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"What do you have there? Looks like it would make good bait."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>cc_Boulder:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"My old friend, the glimmering boulder, has moved on. It may not seem like an important event, but to me it's a big change. I'm happy for the old rock to see more of the world, though."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>MovieInvitation:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Oh... me? I usually wouldn't, but... okay. It's nice of you to think about me. I'll head over there in a little while."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"The crisp air of the wilderness is all I care to know. I live out here by choice."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"...Have you come to ridicule me? I'm just minding my own business."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I don't know you well enough to trust you. Sorry."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"...Hmm? Do you want something from me?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Please don't destroy my tent. It's happened before."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I'm happy by myself, you know. I don't need new friends."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"It would be nice if the townspeople could accept me for who I am. I like living out here in the open air. That's what they don't understand."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"You can learn to survive in the wild. I have. I think we all have a hidden urge to return to nature. It's just a little scary to make the leap."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed6:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I spend a lot of time thinking. If you can fully understand the reasons behind your thoughts, you'll have reached a new level of being."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed2:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I have to be wary of strangers. Most people don't like a 'wild man'."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"The people here seem nice, but they avoid me. People are afraid of the unknown."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"You can learn a lot from trees. Spend time with them and they might tell you their secrets. Go in peace, young one."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I have everything I need to survive, and more. Nature plays a wonderful tune if you can only learn to listen. I also spend a lot of time reading. One of the reasons I stopped in the valley was for the great library."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Someone was throwing rocks at my tent last night... I just had to wait it out. I don't like to stay in one place for too long. There's just too much to experience in the world."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Mon4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"During all these years I've discovered a few secrets about life. You'll have to find out for yourself."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I saw a heron wading gracefully through the morning mist. Such are the treasures of a quiet life. It's so easy to get caught up in the noise of modern life. Your best years will pass you by in a formless blur. That's why you'v got to learn to slow down. "</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Tue4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"How have you been, my young friend?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Wed6:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Ah... summer. The warm sun heats up the cans for me. Then at night I've got a warm meal to look forward to."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Thu4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I have my own reasons for living alone like this. Some things are best left unsaid... I should do some foraging."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Fri4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Whenever you catch a fish, take a moment to thank it for its sacrifice. Even if you don't believe in the spirit of the fish, it's a good mental exercise. We need to be aware of our effect on the environment."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sat4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"You can find rainbow trout in streams right now."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"This is an easier time of year for me. I don't have to worry about staying warm. Plus, the fruits of the wild are growing everywhere."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I've explored deep into the caves. They hold some hidden secrets. Just be cautious if you go in there."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Tue4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Some joker sprayed paint all over my home during the night... It took hours to scrub it off this morning. I need to start gathering lumber for the winter. Do you have enough lumber to keep your house warm?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Wed4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I don't have many responsibilities, so I spend my time thinking. You have to understand your thoughts before you can control them."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I don't like to stay in one place for too long."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sun6:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"There's nothing quite like a feast of wild mushrooms in the fall."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"It can get really cold if you live in a tent."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Tue4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Thanks for not shunning me, @. It takes a lot of wisdom to override your base instincts. I'm a human like everyone else. I just have a different lifestyle."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Wed4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"I'm sure you understand why I'm cautious of strangers. But let's put that in the past, okay? You and I are friends now, I think."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Thu4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Winter is tough, but you can still fish and forage to get by. If you have any animals you should keep them inside."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Fri4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"The trees go to sleep during the winter. It makes it a bit lonely out here. But I wouldn't deny them their beauty sleep."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sat4:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Thanks for stopping by. I was actually feeling a little lonely this morning. So, have you discovered anything interesting in the mines?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">"Sleeping on the ground is good for my back. It's best to look at the positive side of things."</dialogue> </p>

</xml>