
<?xml-model href="MainRNC.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><metadata>xnbData: 
target: "w"
compressed: true
hiDef: true
readerData: 
- 
type: "Microsoft.Xna.Framework.Content.DictionaryReader`2[[System.String, mscorlib, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b77a5c561934e089],[System.String, mscorlib, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b77a5c561934e089]]"
version: 0

- 
type: "Microsoft.Xna.Framework.Content.StringReader"
version: 0


numSharedResources: 0

content:  #!Dictionary&lt;String,String&gt;</metadata>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_0:</context> <dialogue>"Finally... some heavy rain. I get bored of sunny weather easily."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_1:</context> <dialogue>"Hey. I was just thinking about my old room in the basement. I felt comfortable there, but this is a lot more interesting. And I don't miss the smell...#$e#I felt kind of embarrassed living in my mom's house for so long."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_2:</context> <dialogue>"Hey. I couldn't sleep last night so I took a walk to the caves. I found this... want it?[575 769 767 84 66 78]#$e#I just have trouble sleeping sometimes, it has nothing to do with you. I love you.$7"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_3:</context> <dialogue>"Seems like a pretty good day to just lay around, maybe read a book or something... what do you think?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_4:</context> <dialogue>"Hey, another rainy day... perfect.#$e#You look cold... here, come closer.$l"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_0:</context> <dialogue>"I'm trying my best to quit smoking now that we're married... I don't wanna die on you. It's a bad habit.#$e#I want to have a future together.$l"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>patio_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue>"Need something? I'll just be over here working on my bike for a while."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_1:</context> <dialogue>"I did some work on the laptop today. I was actually brainstorming some ideas for a game I want to make.#$e#With your farming income, I can afford to do what I want with my life. It's pretty amazing. Thank you.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_2:</context> <dialogue>"Sorry, I didn't make any dinner. We might have a frozen pizza in the fridge or something.#$e#I dunno, my mind was elsewhere. It's hard to remember to do chores..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_3:</context> <dialogue>"How was your day? Did you slay any monsters?$h#$e#It feels good to take out your aggression now and then, doesn't it?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_4:</context> <dialogue>"Maybe a witch will visit us tonight? Hah.. if only life was that interesting..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_0:</context> <dialogue>"The older I get, the less I'm drawn to the city. It had a certain mystique to it, once. But it turns out that was just a romantic fantasy.#$e#The city's so busy, so full of people... I don't belong there. I'm a loner."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_1:</context> <dialogue>"Hey... want some coffee?[395]$7#$e#I needed some... woke up early from a nightmare and I just couldn't fall back asleep."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_2:</context> <dialogue>"I couldn't sleep last night so I went for a night ride on the motorcycle.#$e#I need to stay independent, even though we're married. That's just how I am. I still love you, though.$7"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_3:</context> <dialogue>"Hey. How'd you sleep last night? I heard you mumbling.#$e#You seemed scared, but I have to admit... it was kind of cute.$l"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_4:</context> <dialogue>"Living here with you is teaching me to come out of my shell a little bit. I think it's good for me.$7"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_0:</context> <dialogue>"Hey. I just hung out around the house, today. Nothing interesting...#$e#...#$e#The view from our house is perfect. You can see the sun setting over Pelican Town from the front porch."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_1:</context> <dialogue>"Maybe I drank too much coffee... I don't feel very tired.#$e#I'm still trying to adjust to the farm schedule. I used to stay up until 5am and sleep in until 2pm, sometimes.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_2:</context> <dialogue>"It's really cool to have our own place. I can do whatever I feel like and not have people nagging at me all the time.#$e#I'm sure Maru's happy that I'm gone."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_3:</context> <dialogue>"I spotted a bat out the window earlier. It's kind of hard to see, but if you stay focused you can often catch them flittering about. They're out there."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_4:</context> <dialogue>"I often felt unappreciated back home... but here I feel like I really belong. Thanks for making me feel welcome, @.$l"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Outdoor_0:</context> <dialogue>"I feel like I want to do something today... but I'm not sure what. Do you ever have that problem, @?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Outdoor_1:</context> <dialogue>"Hmm... sometimes I have to force myself to stay outside for health.#$e#I dunno what it is, but I like being indoors. Maybe I'm just so used to my dark basement."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Outdoor_2:</context> <dialogue>"I'll just watch you from here.$h#$e#I enjoy watching you."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Outdoor_3:</context> <dialogue>"I don't want to get soft now that I'm a married guy. Maybe I should start eating more hot pepper and working out?#$e#Just an idea...$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Outdoor_4:</context> <dialogue>"We should raise more slimes... In big quantities they can be pretty profitable. And they're so easy to raise.#$e#Also, different colored slimes produce different items. I dunno, I think it'd be kind of a fun hobby for us."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>OneKid_0:</context> <dialogue>"I'm still getting used to being a father. Don't worry, I'll take good care of %kid1! It's just... something new."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>OneKid_1:</context> <dialogue>"Maybe when %kid1 is a little older, I'll get a sidecar for the bike and we can all go for a ride.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>OneKid_3:</context> <dialogue>"Have you smelled %kid1? Maybe it's time for a bath..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>TwoKids_0:</context> <dialogue>"Don't worry, I already fed the kids... %kid2 spilled the chocolate milk all over my shirt again."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>TwoKids_1:</context> <dialogue>"I hope %kid1 and %kid2 are nice to each other. Maru and I always fought as kids.#$e#If I think back on it, it was mostly my fault..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>TwoKids_2:</context> <dialogue>"I've had this recurring dream that %kid2 is wearing a shadow shaman costume and sitting on a glowing pumpkin. Weird, huh?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>TwoKids_3:</context> <dialogue>"We've come a long way, @. Look at our family. To be honest, I never really thought I'd end up in this situation.#$e#Now that I'm here, I like it...$l"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_0:</context> <dialogue>"Hey. Look at me. Never forget that I love you... you're everything to me.$l#$b#Now go make us some money.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_1:</context> <dialogue>"Hey... come here. You look great today.$l"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_2:</context> <dialogue>"You always look great, even after slopping around in the yard all day.$l"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_3:</context> <dialogue>"I don't often show it, but I'm really happy that I'm your husband. Marrying you was the best decision I ever made.$l"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_4:</context> <dialogue>"You don't ever have to worry about me. I like to spend a lot of time alone."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_5:</context> <dialogue>"Sometimes I feel so angry... but when you show up I always start to calm down.$7#$e#Maybe I'll mellow out with age."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_6:</context> <dialogue>"I know you're tough, but I still worry about you, sometimes. Don't ever go monster hunting without a life elixir and some sturdy boots, okay?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_8:</context> <dialogue>"I don't really feel like doing work today. Maybe I'll see what's on TV."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Good_9:</context> <dialogue>"I don't really need friends. You're the only person I need in my life. Is that weird?#$e#I guess I'm not like most people."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Neutral_0:</context> <dialogue>"When I take walks I do my best to avoid everyone. I hate being pressured into small talk."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Neutral_2:</context> <dialogue>"Why don't you tell me about your day when we're in bed tonight? I'm kind of busy right now..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Neutral_3:</context> <dialogue>"Are you going into town today? Why, what are you up to?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Neutral_4:</context> <dialogue>"I guess I can do the laundry today... You probably have your hands full with running the farm."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Neutral_5:</context> <dialogue>"Are we doing okay on money? I don't want to have to sell my laptop..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Neutral_6:</context> <dialogue>"If you need to go see your friends in town, go ahead. I like being alone, anyways."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Neutral_8:</context> <dialogue>"House-cleaning isn't fun, but when I listen to music and it goes by pretty fast."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Bad_5:</context> <dialogue>"Look, I just want to be alone. Why don't you go outside and do your own thing for a while?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Bad_6:</context> <dialogue>"What do you want? You sound like my step-dad. Go away.$a"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Bad_7:</context> <dialogue>"This place is starting to feel like a tomb.$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Bad_8:</context> <dialogue>"I started smoking again... I've just been really stressed out lately.$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>funLeave_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue>"I'm going to take a walk today. I need some time to myself. I'll see you in the evening."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>funReturn_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue>"My day was fine, nothing much to tell you about. Why don't you tell me about yours?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="spring">spring_1:</date></context> <dialogue>"Oohh... my head. Happy new year...$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="spring">spring_12:</date></context> <dialogue>"Are you excited for tomorrow's festival? It'll be good to see Sam again."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="spring">spring_23:</date></context> <dialogue>"Oh... tomorrow's the flower dance, isn't it? Do we have to go?#$e#I hate wearing that ridiculous tight jumpsuit. Why does Lewis make us do this?$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_1:</date></context> <dialogue>"Summer's here... I need to start slathering the sunscreen pretty thick if I want to maintain my pale complexion..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_10:</date></context> <dialogue>"Have you thought about what you're going to put in the luau soup?#$e#I have no idea what's good... you're the chef!$7"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_27:</date></context> <dialogue>"The weather's starting to cool off. It feels great.#$e#Should we go to the festival tomorrow night? It's actually a tradition I kind of enjoy.$7"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_1:</date></context> <dialogue>"It seems like the whole valley's changed overnight... I guess fall's finally here."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_15:</date></context> <dialogue>"The Stardew Valley Fair is a little crowded for my tastes... but I'll just hang out with Sam. It'll be good to catch up with him.#$e#You should play some carnival games, though! Don't worry about me.$7"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_26:</date></context> <dialogue>"I'm excited for the Spirit's Eve tomorrow. I wonder what horrors we'll find there.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_1:</date></context> <dialogue>"What are your plans this winter? I know it's more of a laid-back time for you."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_7:</date></context> <dialogue>"Are you going to enter the fishing contest tomorrow?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_28:</date></context> <dialogue>"It's been a great year, @. We should celebrate a little. [346]$h#$e#I'm sure next year will be even better.$7"</dialogue> #!String</p>
</xml>
