<?xml-model href="MainRNC.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>

<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue>"Hey, it's Mr. @, the new farmer! I'm Pierre, owner of the local general store.^Hey, it's Ms. @, the new farmer! I'm Pierre, owner of the local general store.#$b#If you're looking for seeds, my shop is the place to go. I'll also buy produce from you for a good price!#$e#A little agriculture could really inject new life into the local economy!"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Resort:</context> <dialogue>"I'm losing a lot of money being away from the shop...$s#$b#But, you know what? It's worth it."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Resort_Shore:</context> <dialogue>"Mmm... that salty smell of the sea is making me want some sashimi."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Resort_Chair:</context> <dialogue>"Eh, let the kids play in the sun. I'll just sit in this chair."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Resort_Bar:</context> <dialogue>"Drink after drink... Gus must be making a killing!"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>cc_Complete:</context> <dialogue>"This is a dream-come-true! You can't begin to imagine how much stress JojaMart was causing me.#$e#For a small town like this, one store is enough! There's too much social pressure for me to overcharge, anyway."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>joja_Begin:</context> <dialogue>"This is a sad day for Pelican Town... The stronger Joja becomes, the closer I move toward bankruptcy. I might have to sell the shop soon...$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>MovieInvitation:</context> <dialogue>"Hey, that's a great idea... It'll be nice to get out from behind the counter. I'll meet you there!"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue>"Welcome! If you're looking for seeds, you've come to the right place!"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Mon_inlaw_Abigail:</context> <dialogue>"Hello, er... my son?$s^Hello, er... daughter?$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Mon4:</context> <dialogue>"Hi, @. Need any seeds or fruit tree saplings?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Mon4_inlaw_Abigail:</context> <dialogue>"Hi, @. How's Abigail doing? The shop hasn't been the same without her..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue>"Sometimes I get new items in stock, so make sure to stop by every so often.#$e#It's a lot of work to run a shop.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Tue6:</context> <dialogue>"You know, I used to be a pretty good boxer back in the day... my right hook was the stuff of legend!$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue>"It's my day off today.#$e#Hmmm... what to do...$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Wed4:</context> <dialogue>"When I was younger I always had something interesting to do... now I find myself just wasting time whenever I'm not at work.$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue>"I'm happy to buy any produce off you.#$b#I'll give you a fair price, of course!"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Thu2:</context> <dialogue>"I really do appreciate your business, Mr. @. I've been having a harder and harder time turning a decent profit.^I really do appreciate your business, Ms. @. I've been having a harder and harder time turning a decent profit."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Thu8:</context> <dialogue>"#$1 pierre2#Does Abigail look anything like me? Don't tell my wife, but sometimes I wonder if I'm really the father.$k$s#$e#Don't tell my wife, but I hate to cook dinner."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue>"#$1 pierreJoja#Business has been slow since Joja moved into town. It's hard to compete with their selection.$k$s#$e#Hi there. Is your farm doing well?#$e#Maybe a few of my seeds will spruce things up."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue>"If you find any wild produce, I'll take it off your hands for a reasonable price."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Sat8:</context> <dialogue>"I'll tell you a secret. Sometimes, when the store is empty, I'll practice my opera singing behind the counter.$h#$e#Don't tell anyone."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue>"#$1 pierreBlue#*sigh*... I've got those behind-the-counter blues...$k$s#$e#I wish I could go for a walk, but I can't leave the store unattended.#$e#I've heard the flowers are in bloom and the air smells great...$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Wed6:</context> <dialogue>"#$1 pierre1#*sigh*... No matter how well the business does, it's never enough to satisfy my desire for success. What's wrong with me? Maybe I'm just bored with domestic life.$s#$e#Some day I'm going to open a new shop in the city and make a killing.#$e#Unfortunately, business is so slow I can hardly save any money...$s"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Thu4:</context> <dialogue>"Hey, @. You're my number one customer!"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>summer_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"I've got summer seeds available! You'd better stock up."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>summer_Wed:</context> <dialogue>"I'm so glad to have a day off from work."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>summer_Thu:</context> <dialogue>"Everyone's enjoying the weather instead of shopping... *sigh*"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>summer_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"Oh, hi. Are you satisfied with the quality of my summer seeds?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>summer_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"Summer is a good time to eat a refreshing salad, don't you think?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>summer_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"Ugh... It's so hot in here."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>winter_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"You can't grow any crops during winter... so I have no seeds to offer you.#$e#It's really going to cut into our profits."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>winter_Wed:</context> <dialogue>"#$1 pierreDin#I'm going to surprise Caroline tonight with dinner and a bottle of Stardew Red. Don't tell anyone!$k#$e#Finally, a day of relaxation."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>winter_Thu:</context> <dialogue>"Hi. In the mood for a litle shopping?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>winter_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"I mainly deal in edibles, so if you've got any ores or wood you'd better try selling them somewhere else."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>winter_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"Is it just me or is there a cold draft in here?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>winter_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"If I didn't have this shop to run I would be outside right now.#$e#It would be fun to throw a snowball."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>fall_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"Fall seeds are here! Crops don't grow in winter so this is your last shot until spring.#$b#Better go all out, huh?"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>fall_Thu:</context> <dialogue>"It's starting to get cold outside...#$b#That means more people come into the shop to warm up... hehe."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>fall_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"#$1 pierreMEGA#My dream is to keep opening new stores until I become extremely wealthy. hehehe.$k#$e#Hi there. Is your farm still doing well?#$e#Maybe a few of my seeds will spruce things up.$h"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>fall_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"I'm happy to buy whatever you produce on the farm.#$e#Yes, I do resell it for a profit... but that's the benefit of being an established shop owner.#$e#Don't get any ideas..."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>fall_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"If I didn't have this shop to run I would be outside right now...#$e#The leaves look great and the mushrooms are sprouting."</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Event_naga1:</context> <dialogue>"Thanks, I appreciate that. Just forget you ever saw this, okay?$h#$b#...And I'll just forget that you were snooping around in my bedroom!"</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Event_naga2:</context> <dialogue>"You would really do that to me? You're terrible.$s#$b#You shouldn't have been snooping around in my bedroom in the first place! Nosy neighbors are the worst.$3"</dialogue> #!String</p>
</xml>