
<?xml-model href="../RelaxNG/CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>accept_866:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"A Stardew Valley rose? That's so lovely! Thank you! Whenever I miss the valley, I'll smell this rose. Hehe. Here, take this. It's been on the shelf for 10 years and no one has bought it. You can have it!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"Hello hello, sweetie! I'm so glad that the bus is back in service. It was starting to get lonely out here. ...I almost went out of business. Hey, but now you're here to buy a whole bunch of seeds... right, sweetie?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"You can find coconuts and cactus fruits outside. Feel free to take as many as you can find. They're oooh-yummy, too. Heeee!~"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"Why hello there! If you see my friend Emily in town, could you tell her I said 'Hi'? Thanks!"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"That shady-looking guy in the back? I'm not supposed to talk about it. Anyway... what's the weather like in the valley?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"You wouldn't have much luck farming out here, honey. Well, unless you were a cactus farmer."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"Hi! Welcome to Sandy's Oasis, the number one destination in Calico Desert! *whisper* Did I sound professional? Make sure to check out our seasonal seed selection. You look really thirsty. Here, have a taste of this ice cold milk. [184] Tasty, huh?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"It's always sunny here, even in winter! Actually, it's a little hot for my tastes... my delicate skin burns quickly in the sun."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu2:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"That shady-looking guy in the back? I'm really not supposed to talk about it. Anyway... what's the weather like in the valley"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu4:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"Hey... I think I can trust you. You can keep a secret, right? *whisper* That guy in the back... it's some kind of exclusive club. I've never been inside myself, but they pay me a generous monthly rent so I don't ask any questions. SOOOOoo! How's that Stardew Valley weather right now?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri4:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"My name's not really Sandy, you know. It's just good for business. But everyone calls me Sandy anyway, so I've just gotten used to it."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed8:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"Isn't it expensive, coming to the desert so often like you do? You must really like to see me, huh? Hmmm... "</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun8:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"Hi there, honey. Yep, it's just me, alone in this big old shop. Hmmm... Well, except for that creepy guy in the back. But he never moves a muscle, so I often forget about him."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed10:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"Hey, it's @! I'm glad to see you, kid. I was starting to think you'd never come back! If I didn't have this shop to run I'd come back to the valley with you for a day or two... just you and me on the old farm. You'll just have to visit me more often so I don't get depressed."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue10:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">"Hi!~ Stay as long as you like. The air conditioning sure feels nice, doesn't it?"</dialogue> </p>

</xml>