<?xml-model href="CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>

<p><context>name: Stardew Valley Fair</context> </p>
<p><context>conditions: Town/900 1500</context> </p>
<p><context>set-up:</context> fallFest/-1000 -1000/farmer 12 54 1/changeToTemporaryMap Town-Fair/viewport -1000 -1000/loadActors Set-Up/advancedMove Vincent true -3 0 2 5000 3 0 2 5000/advancedMove Jas true 2 0 4 5000 -2 0 4 5000/advancedMove Marnie true -2 0 4 5000 2 0 2 5000/advancedMove Abigail true 4 6000 5 0 0 3 2 6000 0 -3 -5 0/advancedMove Robin true 0 1 1 5000 0 -2 3 5000 0 1 1 5000/animate Sebastian false true 200 16 16 16 16 16 16 16 16 16 16 16 16 17 18 19 20 21 21 21 21 20 22 22 23/addTemporaryActor BabyPig 32 32 65 68 2 false Animal/addTemporaryActor Pig 32 32 65 70 3 false Animal/addTemporaryActor White_Chicken 16 16 59 67 2 false Animal/addTemporaryActor Brown_Chicken 16 16 61 67 2 false Animal/addTemporaryActor White_Cow 32 32 59 72 0 false Animal/addTemporaryActor BabyWhite_Cow 32 32 61 72 1 false Animal/advancedMove BabyPig true 0 1 3 5000 0 -1 0 7000/advancedMove Pig true 3 5000 0 1 1 5000 0 -1 3 5000/advancedMove White_Chicken true 1 0 2 7000 -1 0 2 10000/animate Brown_Chicken false true 500 16 17/viewport 22 22 true unfreeze/globalFadeToClear/pause 2000/playerControl fair </p>
<p><context>Abigail_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">I beat all these games last year!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Leah_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">I learned all of Robin's techniques last year, but she's always one step ahead of me!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Maru_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">mumph... This is my one chance to pig out on barbecue sandwiches.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Penny_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">I hope we win the grange display contest!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Haley_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">Did you remember to bring good stuff for our grange display? I hope we win this year.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sebastian_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">Hey, @. I'm just catching up with Sam. Go ahead and have some fun.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sam_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">Sebastian's the same as always. Are you having fun at the festival?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Alex_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">I'm just catching up with some old friends... you go on and have a good time.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Harvey_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">I'll wait here until you're ready to go home...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Elliott_spouse:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">The smokey aroma drew me here, yet 'twas the zesty sauce that truly sealed my fate... *gurgle*</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">I already beat all the games... now what?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Robin:</context> <dialogue who="Robin">Woodworking is an ancient tradition that I'm very proud to be a part of.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Demetrius:</context> <dialogue who="Demetrius">Robin really works hard on her carpentry stuff... she deserves a little recognition now and then.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">*slurp* mmm... this barbecue sauce is amazing.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">It's kinda hectic today... I'm just gonna hang out here for a while.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Pierre:</context> <dialogue who="Pierre">My store carries the very finest quality products in the whole valley. Please, inspect my grange display closely and see for yourself!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Caroline:</context> <dialogue who="Caroline">Pierre is very serious about his grange display. He's been setting aside the best-looking produce for weeks in preparation. Hey, best of luck to you if you enter!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Linus:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">These animals never judge people by their looks. The same can't be said for humans.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">I played the 'Strength' game too many times and now my arms feel like rubber.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>George:</context> <dialogue who="George">Hmm... smoked turkey haunch? I guess this festival isn't all bad.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Evelyn:</context> <dialogue who="Evelyn">I wish Gus would include a vegetarian option. Some zucchini skewers, maybe?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Lewis:</context> <dialogue who="Lewis">Well @, It's the big day... Our most important festival of the year, the 'Stardew Valley Fair'. If you'd like to participate by setting up a grange display, I've left an empty stand for you. Just let me know after you've set everything up so we can get to the judging.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Clint:</context> <dialogue who="Clint">I complain about my job sometimes, but I do take pride in my work. These are some of my finest pieces. I hope you like them.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">You know, I would've made a pretty good clown. I think I missed my calling.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">I won the wheel of chance ten times in a row and now the man won't let me play anymore...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Pam:</context> <dialogue who="Pam">Better hurry up, kid... Before ol' Pam here fishes every last lunker out of the tent! Hehe.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">Have you been to the fortune teller? She set up her stand in the graveyard. I already saw her... she told me something... interesting. *giggle*</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Jodi:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">He doesn't look very happy... I guess Mayor Lewis had to cut costs with a budget clown this year.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Kent:</context> <dialogue who="Kent">I'm waiting for this clown to start doing something funny. Pretty disappointing.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">Hey @. Having a good time? The slingshot tent is pretty fun, and if you get good at it you can really rack up the star tokens.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">I really admire Robin's carpentry skills. I use a lot of the same techniques in my own line of work.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">All these animals are friendly and love to get massaged.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Marnie:</context> <dialogue who="Marnie">I tried my best, but my display is pretty weak compared to Pierre's. Well, maybe the judges will give me bonus points for the massive cheese wheel.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">I'm trying to get Gus to tell me his sauce recipe, but he won't budge.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Gus:</context> <dialogue who="Gus">Eat as much as you like! It's all free today... compliments of Mayor Lewis. Oh! Make sure to dribble some of my secret sauce on there.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Dwarf:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">You say it's raining up above? *gasp* Rain... It's almost mythical to us. Some of us live our entire lives without ever experiencing it.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wizard:</context> <dialogue who="Wizard">Welwick and I have known each other for a long time... she is a remarkable diviner, and a good friend. ... That clown... I know him from somewhere. Was it the school of illusion? Or maybe the Carnival of Secrets? Hmm...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">And just a few steps over there, Gus is grilling up a batch of pork ribs... Yikes. I've got some soul-searching to do...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sandy:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">I heard it's raining back home. Is that why you came here? I kind of miss the rain, actually...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Jas:</context> <dialogue who="Jas">Ow! A hen pecked my little finger!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Vincent:</context> <dialogue who="Vincent">Moooo!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Marlon:</context> <dialogue who="Marlon">Clint's blades get sharper every year. So do his prices...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Willy:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">Are you setting up a grange display, @? It's your chance to show off all the good produce from !</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Leo:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">Haha! I've never seen anything like this before...</dialogue> </p>
</xml>
