
<?xml-model href="CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"Ahoy there! It's nice to see young folk movin' in to the valley. It's not very common these days."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>accept_869:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"Ah... That's the perfect bait for a catfish I've been tryin' to catch!#$b#Here, let me trade you this for it. I'm not sure what it is, but it washed up on the beach not too long ago.#$b#Somethin' tells me you could use it, lad.^Somethin' tells me you could use it, miss."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>FullCrabPond:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"*sniff*... Ah... That old familiar scent. You've been raisin' crabs, haven't ya?#$b#Yer a man after me own heart, @. Hah!$h^Yer a lady after me own heart, @. Hah!$h#$b#Here, take this. I found it on the beach... Been savin' it fer a special occasion. It's not every day I discover a fellow crab enthusiast! [797]"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>MovieInvitation:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"Ah... a movie. That's kind of ye, lad.^Ah... a movie. That's kind of ye, miss.#$b#I'll just finish me pipe, and head over."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"Ahoy there, son.^Ahoy there, lass.#$b#Looks like decent weather for fishing, eh?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon4:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"Have you had much luck in the local waters? You look like you could be a strong angler if you set your mind to it."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"A true angler has respect for the water... don't you forget that."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue6:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"The ol' Man was a fisherman, you know. I grew up sailing between the fern islands, living from catch to catch.#$e#The fishing life is tough, but there's something about it that keeps you goin'."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"Some fish come and go with the seasons. Others only come out at night or in the rain."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"*mumble* *mumble* ...Eh? I would tell you about my thoughts, but it's a fisherman's secret."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu2:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"There's rumors of some very rare fish in these parts... but only an experienced angler could stand a chance against them.#$e#You'll need the finest bait you can get if you want a rare fish to bite."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"If you really want to get the fish biting, make sure you put some bait on your hook."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"If the local fishing scene got a bit more lively, I might expand the shop's stock."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat8:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"How's the fishing life going for ya?#$e#I try to fish as often as possible, but it's not easy when you've got a shop to run."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"If you purchase a high quality fishing rod, you'll be able to attach bait and tackle to the line.#$b#Bait causes fish to bite faster. Tackle can make your job a lot easier when reeling fish in.#$e#There's all kinds of tackle, with different perks. They're usually a little flimsy, so don't be surprised if your tackle breaks after a while."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun10:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">"Hey, it's my skipper, @!$h#$e#I'd give you a discount on bait if I could afford it.$s"</dialogue> </p>

</xml>