<?xml-model href="LocationSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>

    16253595/j 29/X: "distantBanjo/6 6/farmer 5 9 0 Willy -100 -100 2/skippable/move farmer 0 -1 0/pause 1000/warp Willy 4 4/playsound doorClose/pause 100/<dialogue who="Willy">Ahoy!</dialogue>/pause 500/move Willy 1 0 2/<dialogue who="Willy">Come in... make yourself at home...</dialogue>/move farmer 0 -1 0/move farmer -1 0 3/pause 1000/animate farmer true true 9999 35/playSound quickSlosh/pause 800/playSound quickSlosh/pause 800/<dialogue who="Willy">Aye... that's good stuff, there. The fish go crazy for it. Just... eh... make sure to wash yer hands good after dipping them in those juices...</dialogue>/<dialogue who="Willy">The aroma has been known to linger for up to seven weeks, lad...^The aroma has been known to linger for up to seven weeks, miss...</dialogue>/stopAnimation farmer/startJittering/jump farmer/positionOffset farmer 4 0/pause 50/positionOffset farmer 4 0/pause 50/positionOffset farmer 4 0/pause 50/positionOffset farmer 4 0/pause 50/positionOffset farmer 4 0/pause 50/positionOffset farmer 4 0/pause 50/positionOffset farmer 4 0/pause 50/positionOffset farmer 4 0/pause 50/stopJittering/pause 1000/<dialogue who="Willy">So... you been catching a lot o' fish?</dialogue>/pause 300/stopAnimation farmer/faceDirection farmer 0/pause 500/quickQuestion #Yes#No#It's too difficult...(break)emote Willy 20\\<dialogue who="Willy">Aha! A man after me own heart... Aha! A lady after me own heart...</dialogue>\\pause 500\\<dialogue who="Willy">You can always trust a fisherman...^You can always count on a lady who fishes...</dialogue>\\<dialogue who="Willy">That's what me ol' Pappy used to say, at least. haha! Well, keep it goin'... if you can catch every fish in these waters, I've got a special prize waitin' for ye...</dialogue>(break)emote Willy 28\\<dialogue who="Willy">Not the fishin' type, eh? That's too bad...</dialogue>(break)emote Willy 16\\<dialogue who="Willy">Yes, it's a difficult sport... especially for a beginner. Have you tried the 'Training Rod'? I sell them right here, at a very low price. You should try using a 'Training Rod' until you get a little more experienced.</dialogue>/pause 1500/faceDirection Willy 3/emote Willy 28/quickQuestion #What's wrong?#Everything okay?(break)pause 100(break)pause 100/pause 400/<dialogue who="Willy">Aye... well, business has been tough, lately. It all started about the same time that old community center fell to ruin... me fish just don't sell like they used to... I've been working double-time just to make ends meet!</dialogue>/faceDirection Willy 2/pause 300/<dialogue who="Willy">No time for me own projects... But, if things picked back up around here, I might have the time to show ya somethin'...</dialogue>/move Willy -1 0 0/playMusic none/<dialogue who="Willy">Heh heh... yep. She's back there... an 'old friend' that's seen better days...</dialogue>/pause 500/emote farmer 8/pause 1000/playMusic ocean/playSound shwip/faceDirection Willy 1 true/pause 40/faceDirection Willy 2/<dialogue who="Willy">Some day, lad... you'll see what I mean.^some day, miss... you'll see what I mean.</dialogue>/pause 2000/end" 

</xml>