
<?xml-model href="../RelaxNG/CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">It's raining outside. Make sure you don't catch cold, dear. Stay indoors as much as possible. I worry about you sometimes!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">It's raining! That means we don't have to water the crops today. Nature can be a big help sometimes. Have you fed the animals yet, honey?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Good morning! I woke up early from the sound of the rain and made you some breakfast. [194 195 210 211 216]   Stay warm and don't work too hard. I want you to stay healthy.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">What's on your agenda today, dear? I don't want to go outside in this weather... I'll just do some things around the house. Maybe I'll make something hot for dinner.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_4:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Any dinner requests for tonight?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">Despite all the technology we have, a rainy day is still the best tool for watering crops.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">The countryside looks more interesting on a day like this, don't you think?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">I think I might do some baking today.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">Might want to do some fishing or mining today, huh?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">Hmmph. If this weather keeps up I'll get too pale.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">Make sure you stay dry today, dear. I don't want you to become hypothermic.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">I got up just before dawn and took a walk around the farm. It's really peaceful at that hour.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">Hmm... I guess I'll have to do push-ups and sit-ups indoors today.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">The rain makes me think of my old life by the ocean. Change is part of life. That's okay.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">I might spend some time today fixing any leaks in the roof or the windows.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">I know you pride yourself on your work, but don't overdo it today. Okay, honey?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">The roof's leaking? Ah well... a little mold never hurt anyone.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">The rain makes it feel like we're all alone. I'm cold... Aren't you ready to tuck into bed?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Make sure you change into something warm. I don't want you to get sick. Can you hear the rain pattering on the roof, @?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Ah...The soothing sound of rain overhead... I'm going to sleep well tonight.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">The rain makes our home seem so cozy.It's nights like this I'm glad we have a quality roof.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_4:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I made some soup for dinner. [199 218 219 727 730] You need something hot on a day like this!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_5:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I'm glad you're home... It's a good night to stay inside.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">Were you able to accomplish much today, hun? I tried to fix up some things around the house... you know, just little stuff.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">I'm ready to hop into bed whenever you are. The sound of rain will put us right to sleep.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">Oh... the smell? I tried to do some baking... It didn't work out too well.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">How was your day today, dear? Muddy?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">Hi, honey. I'm so glad you're home. I was starting to get kind of lonely.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">Hi. It's good to see you. I spent the day skimming through some medical journals.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">I'll never grow tired of the rain... especially out here in the countryside.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">Grandma always used to make hot stew on nights like this.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">Sit down, relax! You've got to be tired after trudging through the mud all day.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">Vincent called. He said he misses me and also to tell you hi.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">I just got off the phone with Jas and Marnie. They seem to be having a pretty good time without me.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">Certain spirits only appear in the rain. Maybe you've heard their cries?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Good morning ~&lt; Ready for a hard day's work? I am.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Hi, honey! Smells good, doesn't it? I made you breakfast! [194 195 210 211 216] You need food to stay energized throughout the day.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Did you sleep well? I've got some chores to do in here.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Did you have any strange dreams last night? I did, but all I remember is that it had something to do with a %adj %noun. Weird. Hehe. Dreams don't mean anything... do they, Honey? Well, we can't spend all day chit-chatting. You have work to do!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_4:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Good morning, dear. Another day of farm chores, huh? I'll be cheering for you. &lt;</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">If you ever want to talk about how to maximize crop yield or anything... I'm open to that!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">There's always something new happening on our farm... I love it.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">This place is so big compared to the trailer, I feel overwhelmed... In a good way!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">Mind if I add some architectural flair to the woodwork around here? My chisel hand is itching!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">I always feel happy on a sunny day.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">The sky looks great today... so clear! From now on, I'm only going to go into the clinic when I have appointments. Otherwise I can just work from home!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">Well, this place sure beats my old basement room, doesn't it?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">The sun's shining and I'm bursting with energy! You'd better watch out! Heh Heh.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">I've been keeping a journal ever since we moved in together. Now that I actually have a life, I have lots to write about. I want to make sure I always remember these years.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">There's too much stuff I want to get done today... Maybe I'll just watch TV instead.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">By providing fresh, healthy produce to the community, we're doing a great service!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">There's something special in the air... *sniff*... what is that? Oh... It's just this old corn chip I put in my pocket a few weeks ago. *crunch*</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Did you get everything done today, @? I did some house chores... but now I'm so tired. I'm ready for bed whenever you are.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Wow, you look like you did a lot of work today. Now you should just relax and kick back for the night.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I'm glad you're home. I get kind of scared alone at night.I get lonely at night... ...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Are you done with your work for the day? I'm ready to have some fun. But if you're tired I understand.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_4:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">*phew*! I just finished my chores. Now we can spend some time together. So, tell me about your day. ...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">You look like you're ready for bed, @. Should I lull you to sleep with the technical details of my latest project? *yawn*... To be honest, I'm kind of sleepy too.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">Are you ready for bed soon? I turned on the electric blanket for us...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">Hi there, honey. Ready to spend a quiet evening at home?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">It's so quiet and peaceful in the evening. Nothing to distract you from the experience of living.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">You look like you've been working hard, dear. Let me help you de-stress.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">You look like you could use a good massage tonight. Doctor's orders... It's good for the circulation!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">I may be a reclusive guy, but I'm always happy when you're around. Hi, @. Good to see you. It's comforting when you're around.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">My arms feel a little restless... How about a nice, deep massage?I feel exhausted... That's a good sign! It means I worked hard enough today.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">You always smell so good after a day of hard work. It's your natural musk! You smell sweet, my dear. Like a honeycomb drifting on a pool of spice tea. Come here, let me massage your back. You look tense.You smell sweet, my dear. Like a cinnamon leaf floating in the summer breeze.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">I wonder if the moon is visible tonight? So, did you get everything done on the farm today? If you didn't I won't be mad!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">It's a very cozy house... I like it.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">How was your day? Mine actually went pretty well.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">It's a beautiful day today, isn't it? Days like this make work a little more pleasant.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I'm just going to relax and inspect the farm today, okay? It's just such a nice-looking area.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Hi, honey! If I knew more about farm work I'd help you out more. Sorry! I'll be thinking of you.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I'm just going to do some dusting over here. That should help you out, right? *phew*... it's hot out here.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_4:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Don't overwork yourself, dear. Make sure and take a break every now and then, or get something to eat.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">I like being out here. It's a good place to think about new inventions. I'm still hoping to come up with something to help you out in your work.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">I'm just going to hang out here, okay? There's a lot of interesting bugs and things out here. *chuckle*</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">Looks like a good day to work on my tan, don't you think, sweetheart?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">Wow, this is great! I'm really starting to enjoy life on the farm, @. This is the life I've always dreamed of.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">I'm really happy on our little farm, @.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">This is so different from my old life, but I'm really starting to like it. I feel like I really belong here.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">This is so much nicer than being cooped up in the clinic all day. I love watching you on the farm... hehe</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">Today, I'm going to continue writing my new novel. What better place than our wonderful farm? This is perfect.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">I'm going to get a bunch of exercise today! Haha! I love living on a farm.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">Hey, look at those puffy clouds in the sky, honey! I'm going to watch those for a while, if you don't mind.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">I dunno if my lungs can handle this freshness. I'm still used to JojaAir.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">You're doing great work, @. Keep it up.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>jobLeave_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">I have to go into the clinic today. Have a nice day, okay?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>jobLeave_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">I have to go into town today. Don't work too hard, and eat something good for lunch!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>jobLeave_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">I have to leave for work soon. I'll see you tonight. I'll be thinking of you!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>jobReturn_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">Hi, honey. How was your day? *Phew*... I'm exhausted... My patients are still healthy, so it was a good day.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>jobReturn_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">Good evening. My day was fine, thanks! How was yours? Jas and Vincent weren't behaving very well today. I'm still all wound up...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>jobReturn_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">Well, it was just another boring day at the clinic. Hey. Did you have a more exciting day than me? I hope so. Well, It's time to kick back and relax. Did you leave me any dinner? I'm just looking forward to bed-time.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>OneKid_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Have you spent any time with %kid1 today?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>OneKid_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I wonder if %kid1 will grow up to be a farmer like you?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>OneKid_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Don't worry, I'll feed %kid1 today. You can just focus on running the farm.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>OneKid_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Life's a lot different now that we have a child.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>TwoKids_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I already gave %kid1 and %kid2 their breakfast. They were hungry!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>TwoKids_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">We have to make sure and give %kid1 a lot of attention now that we have %kid2. We don't want any jealousy between them.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>TwoKids_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">You know, I think %kid2 has your nose.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>TwoKids_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">A nice house, two wonderful kids, and a beautiful plot of land. What's left?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">It's hard to believe we're finally married...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">You know, I always had a feeling we'd be together some day.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Are you enjoying the married life, @? I am.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Wow, you look really handsome today!Wow, you look beautiful today.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_4:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">This place is my home now... I'm happy here.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_5:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I was just admiring my wedding amulet... The shell is flawless. It must have cost you a fortune!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_6:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Be careful out there! Sometimes I worry about you falling into a mine shaft.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_7:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">@? I just want to say that I appreciate all the hard work you do for our household.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_8:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Don't worry about me... I know you've got a lot of responsibilities outside of the house. I'm fine in here by myself!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Good_9:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Oh, I'm not bored... I'm just enjoying what we have here. It's a simple life, but I like it.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I hope you'll still like me when I'm old and gray.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Do you think your grandpa would be proud of the work we've done?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Taking a break? I guess being a farmer is easier than I thought...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">If you go into town, make sure and say hi to everyone for me.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_4:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I'll do the laundry tomorrow morning before you get up... that way you won't have any down-time.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_5:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Are we doing okay on money, @?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_6:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I wonder what everyone in town is doing today?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_7:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I don't really feel like doing anything today.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_8:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">No matter how much I clean, the house keeps getting dirty again. I guess farms can be kind of dirty.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Neutral_9:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I wonder if we'll live here our entire lives?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">...Do you still love me?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">*sigh*... Maybe we got married too young.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Are you still happy with me?s</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Did I do something wrong? You've been acting different lately.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_4:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Do you ever wonder what else is out there?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_5:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">You used to be romantic... what happened? I know I'm not as young as I used to be... is that what you married me for?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_6:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">We only have one short life to live... is this the best way to do it?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_7:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I used to be your sweetie... now you only seem to put up with me when I make a hot dinner.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_8:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">You've been so cold to me lately...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Bad_9:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I wonder if I could've done better.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Well, a new year has arrived. Do you have a plan for what you want to accomplish this year? I feel pretty hopeful.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_8:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Now that winter's over, we've got lots of productive weather to look forward to.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_23:</context> <dialogue who="23">I hope you've been practicing your moves... tomorrow is the flower dance!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Make sure you don't get a heat stroke, dear. Drink plenty of water and don't overwork yourself.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_8:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Sorry if I smell... I was sweating all night in the heat.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_15:</context> <dialogue who="15">It's summer... that means the house is full of flies. Don't worry, I'll take care of them.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">This weather feels pretty nice after the heat of summer.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_8:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Winter's just around the corner. We need to double check the heating system, turn off the valves, and check all the insulation in the house. Don't worry, I'll take care of it all.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_15:</context> <dialogue who="15">Have you figured out what you're going to use for our grange display tomorrow?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_26:</context> <dialogue who="26">Should we go to the Spirit's Eve festival tomorrow night?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Brrr.... It's cold. I guess winter has arrived.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_7:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Are you going to enter the fishing contest tomorrow?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_28:</context> <dialogue who="28">Thanks for a great year, @. I'm excited to tackle next year together.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">I'm feeling excited for a new year of farming, @!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">I may like the colder seasons, but by the end I'm always glad to see spring arrive.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">Aren't you glad winter's over, honey? Things seem more hopeful now.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">Don't forget to look for wild horseradish, leeks and dandelions while you're out there!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">I'm so happy to see some greenery after that long white winter.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">Wow, my skin is pale... I guess I'd better help you with some farm work this season.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">Let's plant some healthy vegetables this spring.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">I'm looking forward to a beautiful year on %farm farm.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">Hey @. Let's work hard today!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">*sniff* ... My doze is stubbed up... allergies.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spring_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">Maybe I'll learn a new skill this year...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">It's a good time of year to do some stargazing.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">Oh man... I could go for some chocolate cake.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">You must know by now that summer is my favorite season.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">Nothing pairs so well with summer like a nice sweet wine. Don't you think, honey?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">Are you growing any melons this summer?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">I'm going to stay inside as much as possible this summer.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">Make sure you don't get sunburnt, honey... That can really damage your skin.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">One of the main things I miss about the ocean is the fresh fish.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">I always have the most energy in the summer.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">Summer always makes me want to eat more barbecue.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">Phew! It's hot but it feels great, doesn't it? Maybe we'll see some wild parrots today.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">What's on my agenda today... hmmm...  I think I see some spicy pretzel snacks and a couple of 'cold boys' on the horizon.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">I'm glad I still work at the clinic... It's an important service for the community.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">I hope we're growing pumpkins this year.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">I'm craving cake. But not just any cake... it has to be pink.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">Breathe deep... can you smell that? That tells me it's mushroom season.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">It's so peaceful out here on the farm. I never appreciated nature that much living in town.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">My mother used to always make this delicious pumpkin soup in the fall.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">I could sure go for some wine.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">Ah... Fall. The warm sun drifts low in the sky, casting long shadows over waving fields of gold. It's a beautiful time of year, don't you think?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">I feel weak... I need some protein.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">I wonder what's going on in the rest of the world? We're really secluded here.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">I drank a super-food smoothie this morning and I feel aaah-mazing!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">I think there might be a new species of fungus growing behind my mini-fridge. Ah well, 'tis the season, right?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">Spring is coming soon. I'm really looking forward to having rhubarb pie.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">Remember when we played that 'Prairie King' game together, in my room? Those were good times.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">I was just thinking about the time you helped me open a jar of pickles. We've come a long way since then.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">I always start craving salad in the winter... Inconvenient, I know.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">I'm going to do a lot of reading this winter.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">I wonder what Sam's up to? We used to be really good friends.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">Winter is flu season, so work is probably going to be a lot more stressful. Sorry in advance if I'm grouchy.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">I think I might do some writing this winter. There's not much else to do, anyway.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">I hope my grandparents are doing okay. They used to rely on my help quite a bit. You know, with lifting heavy objects or whatever.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">I've given up on being a musician. I'm a family man now!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">Whoops, my hair is frozen solid again.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">There's a wide, wide world out there... but I'd rather stay in my room.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">I got up early to do a little star-gazing. I hope you don't mind if I spend some time on my projects today, honey.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">I got up a little before you and fed David Jr. He's very active this morning. I hope you don't mind the guinea pig smell.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">Go ahead and start your day, honey. I'm just putting on my make-up. Have any plans for the day?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">One of these days I'll have to do your portrait. The view from this window is inspiring, don't you think?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">I always wanted my very own library. This is so charming. I like to do a little reading first thing in the morning. It gets my brain into gear.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">I'm debating whether I should work or just read comics all day. Hey, do we have any pizza in the freezer? I'm hungry.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">No air-traffic this morning, honey. But it's still fun to break out the equipment now and then. I'm working on a new model plane. It's so much more relaxing here than in my old apartment.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">I think I might do some writing today. Will you be okay without my help?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">Don't ever let me get lazy. I want to stay in good shape for you! There's lots of room here to do my exercises. I'm making more progress than ever!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">The old guitar... I don't have as much drive to play it anymore. That's fine. What's on your agenda today?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">I'm going to spend some time with the parrot today. It breaks my heart that he'll never fly again.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>spouseRoom_Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">Beer or cider? Sometimes life can be challenging. Hi, @. I'll just hang out in here today and uh... maybe sweep the floor a little bit or something.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Day_Krobus:</context> <dialogue who="Krobus">Ah, It's more humid today with the rain... I feel a lot more comfortable.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Rainy_Night_Krobus:</context> <dialogue who="Krobus">The sound of the rain reminds me of the sewers... it's comforting. The sewers were my refuge... I felt safe there. But don't worry... I feel the same way about my new home, too.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Day_Krobus:</context> <dialogue who="Krobus">I wish I could help you on the farm, but I can't go out in the sun...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Indoor_Night_Krobus:</context> <dialogue who="Krobus">Hi, @. Welcome home. You look like you've been working hard out there!</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Outdoor_Krobus:</context> <dialogue who="Krobus">On a day like this, I can enjoy the outdoors with you. This is really nice! Just let me know if you see anyone coming, so I can hide.</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>NoBed_0:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Where am I supposed to sleep...?</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>NoBed_1:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I wasn't able to sleep well last night...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>NoBed_2:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">I had to sleep on the floor last night...</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>NoBed_3:</context> <dialogue who="Universal">Did something happen to our bed...?</dialogue> </p>
</xml>