<?xml-model href="../../CharactersXML/CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Robin:</context> <dialogue who="Robin">This is for me? Wow, I absolutely love it!! Thanks! This is really nice! Um... why? What the...? This is terrible! Thank you. This might come in handy.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Demetrius:</context> <dialogue who="Demetrius">You're giving this to me? This is amazing! Thank you! This is a very interesting specimen. ...What is this? This is disgusting. That was very thoughtful of you. </dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">Is that...? Oh wow, @! This is spectacular! This is a super gift! Thank you! Oh... That's for me? I'll just put it over here... Yuck! You thought I would like this? Thanks.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">I really love this. How did you know? Thanks, I like this. ...? ...I hate this. ...thanks. </dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Linus:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">This is wonderful! You've really made my day special.//This is a great gift. Thank you!/-/Hmm... This doesn't really do much for me.//Why would you give this to me? Do you think I like junk just because I live in a tent? That's terrible. A gift? How nice. </dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Pierre:</context> <dialogue who="Pierre">This is my all-time favorite! Thank you! That's very kind of you. I like this.//This isn't exactly my favorite...//Please, never bring this to me again./ -/A present? Thanks!//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Caroline:</context> <dialogue who="Caroline">You're giving this... to me? I'm speechless. Oh, goodness! Are you sure?/-/No, no, no.../-/This is absolute junk. I'm offended. Oh, that's sweet. Thank you.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">I seriously love this! You're the best, @!//Hey, how'd you know I was hungry? This looks delicious!//What am I supposed to do with this?//What were you thinking? This is awful! You brought me a present? Thanks.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">Hey, awesome! I love this stuff! This is cool! Thanks. Um... Okay. Thanks. Are you serious? This is garbage. Thanks!//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>George:</context> <dialogue who="George">This is my favorite thing! Thank you. Thanks.//That's a terrible gift.//This is probably the worst gift I've ever seen. Thanks a lot.//A gift? Hmm...#$e#Do you want something in return?//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Evelyn:</context> <dialogue who="Evelyn">*gasp*... This is absolutely marvelous!$u#$e#You've made an old lady very happy./ /Oh my, it looks wonderful! That's very kind of you.//Um, Where will I put this?/ /...it smells awful./ /How nice. Thank you, dear.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Lewis:</context> <dialogue who="Lewis">Wow, this is my favorite! Thank you!//Thanks, this is great!//Well, I guess it's the thought that counts.../-/This makes me sick. What a horrendous gift. That's very nice of you. Thanks.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Clint:</context> <dialogue who="Clint">Yes! This is exactly what I've been looking for!//This is a fun gift. Thanks! *Sigh*.../-/This makes me depressed. Thanks. </dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">Thank you! I really love this!//Thank you! This looks special./-/Uh, it's for me? ...Thanks./-/Ugh...I'm sorry, but I absolutely hate this./ /Thanks, this looks nice.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Pam:</context> <dialogue who="Pam">Hey, hey! Now this is really something! Thanks a million, kid./ /You did good with this one, kid. Thanks!/-/This just ain't my thing.//Now this is just absolutely despicable.$u#$e#(Is this some kind of mean joke?) Thanks, kid. </dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">This gift is fabulous! Thank you so much!//Thank you! I'm feeling a positive energy from this gift.//Sorry, @. I don't like this./ /This gift has a strong negative energy. I can't stand it. Thanks!//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">Oh my god, this is my favorite thing!!/ /*gasp*...for me? Thank you!//Ugh...that's such a stupid gift./--/Gross!/-/Thank you. I love presents.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Jas:</context> <dialogue who="Jas">*gasp*...Wow!! Thank you!$h I love presents! Thank you!//Is this a gift? Oh...$s//Ew. This is icky.$s/ -/Thank you!//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Vincent:</context> <dialogue who="Vincent">Wow, thank you so much! This is terrific!//For me? Wow, thanks!/ /This isn't very fun...$s//Yuck, what is this?$s/ -/Thanks!//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Jodi:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">Oh, you're such a sweetheart! I really love this!/ /Thank you! This makes my day really special.//Hmm, well I guess I could always put this in the compost...//*Blech*... I hate this...//That's so nice of you! Thanks.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Kent:</context> <dialogue who="Kent">Oh...! Mom used to give me this when I was a young boy. It brings back wonderful memories. Thank you. Hey, now this is a really great gift. Thanks.//Ah... It's a... what is this, exactly? Hmm... This... They gave this to me in Gotoro prison camp. I've been trying to forget about that. *shudder*/-/That's kind of you. The family will like this.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">Aw, yea! This is my absolute favorite!/ /Thanks! I really like this./-/Hmm.. this is... interesting./--/You really don't get it, huh?/ /You got that for me? Thanks!//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">Oh! This is exactly what I wanted! Thank you!/ /This is a really nice gift! Thank you!//Hmm... I guess everyone has different tastes.//This is a pretty terrible gift, isn't it?//Thank you.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">Oh wow, @! How'd you know this is my favorite? This is great! Thanks!//I don't really like this./-/Why are you giving me your garbage? Oh, you got me something? Thanks!//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Marnie:</context> <dialogue who="Marnie">This is an incredible gift! Thanks!! Thank you!/-/Oh. I guess I'll take it. This is worthless. I don't understand you. Thank you! This looks nice.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">@, this is a beautiful gift! Thank you!/ /This is for me? Marvelous!//Hmm... I'm not a huge fan of this./ -/This item gives me a terrible feeling. I'll have to dispose of it. Oh, a present! Thank you! </dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Gus:</context> <dialogue who="Gus">You're giving this... to me? I'm speechless.//Oh, goodness! Are you sure?//No, no, no... This is absolute junk. I'm offended.//Oh, that's sweet. Thank you.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Dwarf:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">Hey, I really love this stuff. You can find great things in the mines./ /Ah, this reminds me of home./ /Hmm... Is this what humans like?/-/I don't care what species you are. This is worthless garbage.//An offering! Thank you. </dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wizard:</context> <dialogue who="Wizard">Ahh, this is imbued with potent arcane energies. It's very useful for my studies. Thank you! Many thanks. This item has some very interesting properties.//This?... I suppose I'll cast it into the flames and see what happens./-/Ughh... These are utterly mundane. Please refrain from bothering me with this in the future.//Thank you. This will prove useful, I think.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">It's for me? This is my favorite stuff! It's like you read my mind.//That's such a nice gift. Thank you!//Hmm... Are you sure this is healthy?/-/...I think I'm allergic to this.//Thanks. That's very kind of you.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sandy:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">Ooo! I absolutely love getting flowers from the valley. I'm so happy!~ This looks wonderful. Thanks so much!//Oh... Um. Thanks./-/*sniff* ...what is it?//This is for me? Thank you!//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Willy:</context> <dialogue who="Willy">This is great! If only me ol' Pappy was around. He'd go nuts for this./ /This looks great. Thank you!/ /Hmmm... You like stuff like this? Huh.//... *sniff*... Well I guess I can toss it into the chum bucket.//A gift! Thanks.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Krobus:</context> <dialogue who="Krobus">This is an amazing gift. For my people it is a great honor to receive something like this./ /Thank you very much. Humans have... interesting tastes./-/Oh... Um. I guess I'll accept it.//Thank you.//</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Leo:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">I love this. I'm going to put it in my nest. Are you sure? This is so nice.../ /Oh... I don't know if I can digest this...//*sniff* *sniff*... Why are you giving this to me? Do you want me to bury it for you?/ /I accept your gift.//</dialogue> </p>
</xml>