
<?xml-model href="../CharactersXML/CharacterSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Abigail:</context> <dialogue who="Abigail">The valley looks more interesting in the rain... don't you think?</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Robin:</context> <dialogue who="Robin">The rain doesn't stop me from getting a job done!$h#$e#Although soggy wood isn't a joy to work with.$s</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Demetrius:</context> <dialogue who="Demetrius">Greetings. Stay inside if you want to keep warm.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Maru:</context> <dialogue who="Maru">When it rains I have a good excuse to work on my gadgets all day.$h#$e#It must be kind of boring for you, though.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Sebastian:</context> <dialogue who="Sebastian">If you're lucky, you might see a frog in this weather.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Linus:</context> <dialogue who="Linus">A warm rain is a pleasant way to get clean.$h</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Pierre:</context> <dialogue who="Pierre">Most people stay indoors on days like this... It's not good for business.$s</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Caroline:</context> <dialogue who="Caroline">My garden is happy today.$h#$e#...and our water bill will be lower this month.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Alex:</context> <dialogue who="Alex">Hmmph. This is not good weather for sports.$s#$e#Oh well, I can always lift weights inside.$h</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>George:</context> <dialogue who="George">It's awful cold, isn't it? What a rotten day.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Evelyn:</context> <dialogue who="Evelyn">When I woke up I heard dripping from somewhere... I think the roof might be leaking.$s#$e#In the old days, George would've scampered right up and fixed it... *sigh*$s</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Lewis:</context> <dialogue who="Lewis">Hi there, @. Taking a break?#$e#I hope the river doesn't overflow...$s</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Clint:</context> <dialogue who="Clint">Today would be a good day to explore the mines... Who knows, you might find some rare ores.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Penny:</context> <dialogue who="Penny">The raindrops are really loud on the metal roof of our trailer.#$e#...It's soothing, though.$h</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Pam:</context> <dialogue who="Pam">Howdy, kid. Stayin' dry?</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Emily:</context> <dialogue who="Emily">It never rains in Calico Desert... That's where my friend Sandy lives.#$e#I wish I could've visited her today.$s</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Haley:</context> <dialogue who="Haley">I spent all morning doing my hair... now the rain could mess it up.$s#$e#*sigh* ... Life is hard sometimes.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Jodi:</context> <dialogue who="Jodi">Did you wipe your boots off before coming in? Sorry... I just cleaned the floor.#$e#But you're always welcome in here! Heh.$h</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Sam:</context> <dialogue who="Sam">Rain muffles sound, so I can play my guitar louder without my Mom getting mad. Hehe.$h</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Leah:</context> <dialogue who="Leah">Maybe I should cook something new and exciting today. Something spicy.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Shane:</context> <dialogue who="Shane">Hmm... this weather makes me thirsty.$s</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Marnie:</context> <dialogue who="Marnie">Hi @. You look like you're soaked...you poor thing!$h</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Elliott:</context> <dialogue who="Elliott">Sometimes when I lay in bed I can hear a distant foghorn cut through the rain.#$b#But when I look out the window I see only a curtain of gray.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Gus:</context> <dialogue who="Gus">There's nothing like a glass of dry red wine on a day like this, huh?#$e#I love my job. Hehehe.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Dwarf:</context> <dialogue who="Dwarf">Rain... It's almost mythical to us. Some of us dwarves live our entire lives without ever experiencing it.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Wizard:</context> <dialogue who="Wizard">Stormy days are the only time I can commune with certain elementals.#$e#I don't expect you to understand.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Harvey:</context> <dialogue who="Harvey">Hi @! Er... Read anything interesting in the library lately?#$e#Heh. Well, um... I'll see you around then?$u</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Sandy:</context> <dialogue who="Sandy">I heard it's raining back home. Is that why you came here?$h#$e#I kind of miss the rain, actually...$s</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Krobus:</context> <dialogue who="Krobus">Ah, the sewers are flowing quickly today. It'll get nice and humid in here... Just how I like it.</dialogue> #!String</p>
<p><context>Leo:</context> <dialogue who="Leo">The valley is peaceful when it rains.#$e#To me... nature is someone I know, with different moods.</dialogue> #!String</p>
</xml>