
<?xml-model href="MainRNC.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
<p><context>Introduction:</context> <dialogue>"Hello, it's nice to meet you. $h#$e#You picked a good time to move here... The spring is lovely."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Entering:</context> <dialogue>"Don't tell anyone, but Willy let me steer the boat for a few minutes.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Leaving:</context> <dialogue>"Well, that was deeply relaxing."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort:</context> <dialogue>"I love the weather in Stardew Valley, but seeing a different climate now and then helps put things into perspective."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Shore:</context> <dialogue>"The shape of the waves here is awe inspiring.#$e#I wonder if I could ever capture that sort of formlessness in a sculpture."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Chair:</context> <dialogue>"I like the heat as long as I'm keeping perfectly still.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Wander:</context> <dialogue>"Mmm, I bet the trees around here would make for an interesting medium to work with.#$e#Though Willy probably wouldn't be happy with me if I dragged a bunch of logs onto his ship!$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Wander_2:</context> <dialogue>"I wonder what kind of things you could forage out here.#$e#I think I saw some tasty looking walnuts growing on a bush nearby."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Resort_Bar:</context> <dialogue>"Have you tried the Piña Colada? I'm on my second one... hehe."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>danceRejection:</context> <dialogue>"I'll be honest. I don't want to dance with you.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>divorced:</context> <dialogue>"I've realized I'm happier by myself. So just leave me be.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>breakUp:</context> <dialogue>"Ohh... Got it. Hah... I really don't have any luck when it comes to this stuff...$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>dumped_Girls:</context> <dialogue>"I don't want to see you for a while...$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>secondChance_Girls:</context> <dialogue>"You caused a lot of grief with what you did... but I'm ready to put the past behind us.$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Beach:</context> <dialogue>"I came for the sound of the ocean. Beautiful, isn't it?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon:</context> <dialogue>"The trees look nice today, don't they?#$q 21/22/211132 Mon_old#So why did you become a farmer?#$r 21 -5 Mon_21#I want to make tons of money.#$r 22 5 Mon_22#It's more \"real\" than living in the city.#$r 211132 5 Mon_211132#To follow in grandpa's footsteps.#$r 22 5 Mon_22#I wanted to escape my old life."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon_old:</context> <dialogue>"$p 21#So are you making as much money as you hoped?|Spending time in nature is very rewarding."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon_21:</context> <dialogue>"Hmm. That seems kind of shallow, doesn't it?$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon_22:</context> <dialogue>"That's pretty much the reason I came here, too!$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Mon_211132:</context> <dialogue>"That's very sweet to honor your grandfather like that."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue4:</context> <dialogue>"Hi. Oh, you want to talk?#$e#The landscape around here gives me a lot of ideas. The terrain is almost like a sculpture itself.#$e#I don't make art for money. It's just an urge that I have.#$e#Farming seems like a very rewarding profession. You get to create delicious food for everyone!$h#$e#You're probably busy. Sorry."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Tue:</context> <dialogue>"Hello, neighbor.#$e#We both live outside of town. Does that mean something?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed:</context> <dialogue>"#$1 LeahBug#This morning I accidentally stepped on a bug.$s#$e#Sometimes I think it's impossible to live without destroying nature in some way."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed6:</context> <dialogue>"I love being around animals. They're so innocent.#$e#Farm animals are wonderful, too.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Wed8:</context> <dialogue>"Hi @! I was just thinking about you and your farm.#$e#I was imagining how good it must feel to harvest a big bunch of crops.$h#$e#Wouldn't it be nice to have help, though?$l"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu:</context> <dialogue>"There's actually a lot of wild food in this area, if you know where to look.#$e#I've been having fresh salads almost every day.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Thu6:</context> <dialogue>"Foraging is a specialty of mine. Someday I'll make you a fresh salad.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri:</context> <dialogue>"It's simpler to be friends with the trees. They don't have much to say.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri2:</context> <dialogue>"We wouldn't be able to survive without nature. It's good to remember that."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Fri4:</context> <dialogue>"Hello, @. It's a nice day, isn't it?#$e#Stop by my cabin if you ever need someone to talk to.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat:</context> <dialogue>"I love to decorate for the different seasons."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sat8:</context> <dialogue>"Farming sounds so fun. I want to try it, someday.$l"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun:</context> <dialogue>"If you hear any banging from inside my hut, it's probably just me working on one of my sculptures."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>Sun8:</context> <dialogue>"If you ever find any interesting looking driftwood, I could use it.#$e#It would be special that you gave it to me.$l"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_sculpt1:</event></context> <dialogue>"...What?$7#$b#Oh! Yeah, that's absolutely right!$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_sculpt2:</event></context> <dialogue>"There's nothing wrong with that... I think there's lots of beauty to be found in raw, untouched nature!#$b#But as a human, I'm also interested in how we shape and interpret the world around us... I guess what I'm saying is that I'm interested in 'art'."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_sculpt3:</event></context> <dialogue>"You pig!%fork$a^Oh! You're...? Me too.$6#$b#Get out!$a^That's good to know.$l"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_parents1:</event></context> <dialogue>"You're right... I just wouldn't have been happy back there.$u#$b#It was better for both of us... to end an unsustainable relationship while we were still young and flexible.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_parents2:</event></context> <dialogue>"That's a little harsh... but, yeah. We had different priorities.$u"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_parents3:</event></context> <dialogue>"Oh yeah? Well maybe I'll just leave, then!%fork$a"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_parents4:</event></context> <dialogue>"*sigh*...$s#$b#I guess you're right... it was kind of selfish. But can you really blame me for wanting to be happy? Ugh... I don't know...$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><event>event_parents5:</event></context> <dialogue>"*sigh*...$s#$b#Maybe you're right... Humans are selfish creatures. I don't know. $s#$b#I probably shouldn't dwell on it. We all have to make hard choices from time to time.$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_1:</date></context> <dialogue>"You can tell it's summer by the sweet smell of nectar wafting through the air!$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"I found some wild fruits this morning!#$e#Sorry, I don't have any left.$s#$e#Keep looking, I'm sure you'll find something."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Tue:</context> <dialogue>"The sound of farm animals is great, isn't it?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Tue4:</date></context> <dialogue>"The simple things in life are best: a soft summer breeze, majestic clouds, and a goblet full of Stardew Valley red."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Thu6:</date></context> <dialogue>"I have a good eye for wild fruit. Some day I'll make you a nice fruit salad.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"You can use a tapper to harvest syrups and other useful liquids directly from trees.#$e#It's a slow process, but the result can be quite valuable."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Fri2:</date></context> <dialogue>"I hate to be blunt, but if we don't treat nature with respect, our grandchildren will be doomed.#$e#Don't you think so?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="summer">summer_Fri6:</date></context> <dialogue>"Hello, @. Do you ever get lonely on that big farm?#$e#Stop by my cabin if you ever need someone to talk to.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"The flowing water keeps my house a little bit cooler in summer.#$e#I can't tolerate heat very well."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>summer_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"What should I do on such a warm, lazy day? *sigh*#$e#Any ideas?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_1:</date></context> <dialogue>"How quickly the seasons change!#$e#It's shocking."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"#$c .5#I found some wild mushrooms over the weekend!#$e#I had a huge plate of wild mushrooms and eggs for breakfast today... I'm still full.#$e#Keep your nose to the ground and you'll find some mushrooms yourself... I'm sure of it."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Tue:</context> <dialogue>"I wonder if I could make a collage out of dried leaves?#$e#They're just so colorful... I can't help but think of the potential for art projects.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Tue4:</date></context> <dialogue>"Everyone has a unique and interesting perspective, whether they believe it or not. Don't you think so?#$e#Although, some people have opinions that I just can't respect."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Wed:</context> <dialogue>"It's so nice to live by the river.#$e#I fall asleep to the soothing sound of water every night."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Thu6:</date></context> <dialogue>"One of these days I'll have to make you a wild mushroom stir-fry.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"Do you have a kitchen in your house?#$e#If you have a kitchen, you can cook all kinds of delicious meals.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="fall">fall_Fri6:</date></context> <dialogue>"Stop by my cabin if you ever need someone to talk to.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"Decorations accentuate the feeling of the season. I think it's a worthwhile tradition."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>fall_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"There's a lot of good places to walk around here.#$e#It feels good to stretch your legs."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Mon:</context> <dialogue>"I love the way everything looks when it's covered with fresh snow."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Tue:</context> <dialogue>"It gets pretty cold in my little cabin.$s#$e#I just snuggle up under a huge blanket, and I'm okay.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Wed:</context> <dialogue>"I saw a snow rabbit early this morning! They're rare, aren't they?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Thu:</context> <dialogue>"I'm having a hard time finding fresh food to eat.#$e#I've been eating a lot of bread.$s"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_Thu6:</date></context> <dialogue>"*Sigh*... It's hard to get fresh food in the winter.#$e#I bet your farm is pretty well stocked with food, huh?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Fri:</context> <dialogue>"Time seems to move slower here.#$e#When I lived in the city, the year went by so fast."</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_Fri6:</date></context> <dialogue>"Do you ever get cold in that farmhouse of yours?#$e#Stop by my cabin if you want to huddle under one of my quilts and drink cider.$h"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sat:</context> <dialogue>"Hello. Do you want something?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context><date season="winter">winter_Sat2:</date></context> <dialogue>"Hello, @. Is there something you wanted to talk about?"</dialogue> </p>
<p><context>winter_Sun:</context> <dialogue>"Do you ever take a whole day off?#$e#It's a refreshing break."</dialogue> </p>
</xml>
